Kacie Hatley

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

C

704-985-2663



kaciehatley@gmail.com



Charlotte, NC



Linkedin.com/in/kacie-hatley

EDUCATION

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP Continuing Education UNC Charlotte Oct 2019 – Apr 2020

ELEMENTARY EDUCATION
Bachelors of Science
Wingate University
Aug 2013 – May 2016

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- CSS Frameworks (Bootstrap & Materialize)
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- JSON
- NPM
- OOJS
- REST API
- MySQL
- ORM (Sequelize)
- Python
- Git Version Control

PROFILE

Entry-level, full-stack developer with 4 years of professional experience as a leader in the field of education. Well-known amongst colleagues for strong work ethic, creativity, and adaptability. Eager to find creative solutions to complex problems. Currently in search for entry-level internship or full-time position—front-end, back-end, and full stack.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

4-H Youth Development Agent

NC State University | Albemarle, NC | June 2017-Present

Created relevant programming for youth in community using research-based curriculum

- Led afterschool Python coding club for middle-school aged youth
- Taught computational thinking skills via Scratch and promoted software/web development as a career in STEM classes throughout community
- Designed print & online resources that have been used statewide (using tools such as Adobe and Canva)
- Increased programs contacts by 700%, outreach by 56%, and social media following by over 200% within first 18 months in position.
- Managed \$24,000 program budget and conserved budget by securing over \$10,000 of in-kind donations
- Supervised over 150 volunteers by developing trainings, providing support, and evaluating performance
- Led trainings for 50+ colleagues as a result of programmatic successes

Classroom Teacher

Stanly County Schools | Norwood, NC | July 2016-June 2017

Used quick decisions and quality materials to enhance the minds and lives of 21 first-grade youth.

- Trained staff in various technologies to enhance classroom instruction
- Streamlined lesson-planning by organizing grade levels' Google Drive

KEY SKILLS

- Bug-Fixing and Troubleshooting: Skilled in methodically testing/identifying issues within front and back-end code
- **Web applications:** Created numerous sleek, full-stack web applications by integrating a wide variety of technologies
- Video Production: Attended video production training through North Carolina State University; trained local businesses and not-profits in video production and video marketing
- Written Materials: Published numerous articles on the North Carolina State University website; proofed and edited written materials for coworkers and supervisor
- Public Speaking: Delivered formal presentations to multiple grant allocations committees, steering committees, and public officials